fastreact.co.uk 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy - FastReact

This privacy policy sets out how “Fast React Systems Ltd” uses and protects any information that you give “Fast React Systems Ltd” when you use this website.

“Fast React Systems Ltd” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

“Fast React Systems Ltd” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 18 June 2007.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@fastreact.co.uk

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Evolution House, Stephensons Way, The Wyvern, Derby, DE21 6LY.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Fast React** are specialist providers of Planning, Sourcing and Critical Path Management solutions specifically developed for the Apparel, Textiles and Footwear sectors where tight margins and short lead-times are commonplace.

## Latest News

Esquel Group, one of the world’s largest producers of apparel for brands including Hugo Boss, Nike, Polo Ralph Lauren and Lacoste has signed a deal to use FastReact’s planning software as part of ambitious plans for the growth and increased productivity of its business. Work has already begun on rolling out the software which will centralise its capacity management and production planning capabilities across its manufacturing facilities in China, Malaysia, Mauritius, Sri Lanka and Vietnam. [More...](http://www.fastreact.com/news-item/global-apparel-manufacturer-esquel-group-adopts-uk-system-to-support-growth-plan/204)

[](http://www.fastreact.com/includes/news_rss.xml) | What is RSS?
